Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - T-Z
        - Withers, Bill - Watching you watching me, 1985; SR-29338; Withers, Bill (Box 79)
          Catalog # CBS 26200; A-side Matrix # 01-26200-1A-1
        - Withers, Bill - Bill Withers live at Carnegie Hall (Disc one), 1973; SR-29339; Withers, Bill (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29340. Double album.
          Catalog # SXBS 7025-2; A-side Matrix # SXBS-7025-AA
          Sussex
        - Withers, Bill - Bill Withers live at Carnegie Hall (Disc two), 1973; SR-29340; Withers, Bill (Box 79)
          In same jacket as # SR-29339. Double album.
          Catalog # SXBS 7025-2; A-side Matrix # SXBS-7025-BB
        - Wizard of Oh - Off to demention x; Titanium white, 1996; SR-29341; Wizard of Oh (Box 79)
          Catalog # TR 003; A-side Matrix # 9511x41A 2003 AR
          Tricked Out Recordings
        - W. L. D. (we love disco) - Dreaming away, 1991; SR-29342; W. L. D. (we love disco); Jenny G (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29343. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DRX 310191; A-side Matrix # DRX 310191 A
          Doremix Records
        - W. L. D. (we love disco) - Dreaming away, 1991; SR-29343; W. L. D. (we love disco); Jenny G (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29342. 2 copies.
        - Wolfman Jack - Fun & romance, 1975; SR-29344; Wolfman Jack (Box 80)
          Catalog # KC 33501; A-side Matrix # PAL 33501-2B
        - Womack & Womack - Starbright, 1986; SR-29345; Womack & Womack (Box 80)
          Catalog # 24 0656 1; A-side Matrix # 2406561-A1
          Manhattan Records
        - Womack, Bobby - My prescription, 1970; SR-29346; Womack, Bobby (Box 80)
          Catalog # LP-24027; A-side Matrix # LP 24027-1-REI
          Minit
        - Womack, Bobby - The poet, 1981; SR-29347; Womack, Bobby (Box 80)
          Catalog # BG10000; A-side Matrix # K13393 BG-10000-A
          Beverly Glen Music
        - Womack, Bobby - Home is where the heart is, 1976; SR-29348; Womack, Bobby; Brotherhood (Box 80)
          Catalog # PC 34384; A-side Matrix # AL-34384-2A
        - Wonder Project - Serving you, 1998; SR-29349; Wonder Project (Box 80)
          Catalog # PP 005; A-side Matrix # PP 005 A
          Poop! Productions
          North Carolina
        - Wonder, Stevie - In square circle, 1985; SR-29350; Wonder, Stevie (Box 80)
          Catalog # 6134TL; A-side Matrix # #13 6134-TL-RE-I-A-15B SLM 10504 WGLW 1-2
          Tamla
        - Wonder, Stevie - Hotter than July, 1980; SR-29351; Wonder, Stevie (Box 80)
          Catalog # 2-47.065; A-side Matrix # 247065 A S. WONDER SIDE ONE SPAIN PRECISION LACQUER
          Spain
        - Wonderland Band - Wonder Woman, 1979; SR-29352; Wonderland Band (Box 80)
          Catalog # BXL1-3390; A-side Matrix # BXL1-3390-A 1
        - Woo, Gerry - How long, 1987; SR-29353; Woo, Gerry (Box 80)
          Catalog # 887 126-1 REV; A-side Matrix # 887-126-1-REV-AS-SP3 1-1 STERLING
        - Woods Empire - The boogie's gonna get you, 1981; SR-29354; Woods Empire (Box 80)
          Catalog # 4Z8 02026; A-side Matrix # 4Z8-02026-3AD MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
          Tabu Records
        - Woods, Ren - Azz izz, 1982; SR-29355; Woods, Ren (Box 80)
          Catalog # E1-60006; A-side Matrix # E1-60006-A-1SP
        - Woods, Stevie - Take me to your heaven, 1981; SR-29356; Woods, Stevie (Box 80)
          Catalog # SD 5229; A-side Matrix # 0-3 SM4-2 ST-CTN-814803-A MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
        - World Class Wreckin' Cru - Lovers; Lonzoland, 1988; SR-29357; World Class Wreckin' Cru (Box 80)
          Catalog # LHR 7001; A-side Matrix # LHR-7001-A L-31413
          Lon Hop Records
        - Wright, Bernard - Funky beat, 1983; SR-29358; Wright, Bernard (Box 80)
          Catalog # AL8-8103; A-side Matrix # STERLING AL8-8103-SA"-ES1 STERLING
        - Wright, Charles - Ninety day cycle people, 1974; SR-29359; Wright, Charles (Box 80)
          Catalog # DSD-50187; A-side Matrix # DSD-50187-A 4
          ABC/Dunhill
        - Wright, Charles - Rhythm and poetry, 1972; SR-29360; Wright, Charles (Box 80)
          Catalog # BS 2620; A-side Matrix # SBS-2620 40176-A 1B
        - Wu-Tang Clan - Reunited - remixes, 1998; SR-29365; Wu-Tang Clan (Box 80)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # B811280-01 A1 MK
        - W.W.W - Cloching; Logan, 1996; SR-29361; W.W.W (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29362. Different discs.
          Catalog # GL 011; A-side Matrix # GL 011A -1
          Grand Larceny
        - Death in Vegas - Rekkit - death by a thousand cuts, 1997; SR-29362; Death in Vegas (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29361. Different discs.
          Catalog # HARD 23 12X; A-side Matrix # HARD 2312XA1 THE EXCHANGE - NiLZ
          Concrete
        - Wynne, Philippe - Wynne jammin', 1980; SR-29363; Wynne, Philippe (Box 80)
          Catalog # JZ 36843; A-side Matrix # PAL-36843-1D MASTERED AT ALLEN ZENTZ L.A., CALIF.
          Uncle Jam
        - Wynters, Gail - Let the lady sing, 1977; SR-29364; Wynters, Gail (Box 80)
          Catalog # APL1-2285; A-side Matrix # A1G APL1-2285A-2
        - X-Clan - Xodus, 1992; SR-29406; X-Clan (Box 80)
          Catalog # 863 033-1; A-side Matrix # 863-099-1 DMS CC CLOSE THE CRACK HOUSE
        - X-Clan - Xodus-The New Testament, 1992; SR-29407; X-Clan (Box 80)
          Catalog # 314 513 225; A-side Matrix # 314-513-225-A-DMM SP
        - X-Clan - To the east, Blackwards, 1990; SR-29408; X-Clan (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29409. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 444 019-4; A-side Matrix # 162-444 019-1-A
        - X-Clan - To the east, Blackwards, 1990; SR-29409; X-Clan (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29408. 2 copies.
        - X-Ray Connection - Replay, 1983; SR-29410; X-Ray Connection (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29411. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DS 422; A-side Matrix # A-1 DS-422-A
          Dance-Sing Records
          Farmingdale, New York
        - X-Ray Connection - Replay, 1983; SR-29411; X-Ray Connection (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29410. 2 copies.
        - Xalam - Xarit, 1988; SR-29412; Xalam (Box 80)
          Catalog # 209009; A-side Matrix # XALAM 209009 A
          Jetset
        - Xavion - Burnin' hot, 1984; SR-29413; Xavion (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29414. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 60375-1; A-side Matrix # ST AM 60375A 5
          Asylum Records
        - Xavion - Burnin' hot, 1984; SR-29414; Xavion (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29413. 2 copies.
        - Y?N-Vee - Chocolate, 1994; SR-29415; Y?N-Vee; Y.N.V. (Box 80)
          Catalog # 853 503; A-side Matrix # 853-503-1A
          Rush Associated Labels
        - Ya-Boyy - What's up; I'm a thug, 2000; SR-29416; Ya-Boyy (Box 80)
          Catalog # ISA 12IN00707; A-side Matrix # WHATS UP A
          Isa Bomb! Records Inc.
          Tampa, Florida
        - Yankovic, "Weird Al" - "Weird Al" Yankovic, 1983; SR-29417; Yankovic, "Weird Al" (Box 80)
          Catalog # BFZ 38679; A-side Matrix # AL 38679 1A
          Rock 'n' Roll Records
        - Yarbrough & Peoples - Be a winner, 1984; SR-29418; Yarbrough & Peoples (Box 80)
          Catalog # TEL8-5700; A-side Matrix # TEL8-5700-SA = 1
          Total Experience Records
        - Yarbrough & Peoples - Be a winner, 1984; SR-29419; Yarbrough & Peoples (Box 80)
        - Yazid - Je suis l'arabe, 1996; SR-29420; Yazid (Box 80)
          Catalog # BIAS 335; A-side Matrix # DF1 96 -9 BIAS 335 LP A
          PIAS France
        - Yello - Pumping velvet; No more words; Lost again; Bostich, 1983; SR-29421; Yello (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29422. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 4939; A-side Matrix # ST-ED 669-79A-2
        - Yello - Pumping velvet; No more words; Lost again; Bostich, 1983; SR-29422; Yello (Box 80)
          In same jacket as # SR-29421. 2 copies.
        - Yellowman - Galong galong galong, 1985; SR-29423; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # GREL 87; A-side Matrix # GREL-87A
          Greensleeves Records
          Ho-Ho-Kus, New Jersey
        - Yellowman - Walking jewellery store, 1985; SR-29424; Yellowman; Sly & Robbie; Taxi Gang (Box 80)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # DS2 SL69 A YELLOW MAN
          Power House
        - Yellowman - Don't burn it down, 1988; SR-29425; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # Shanachie-43049; A-side Matrix # 47982-A SH-43049-A
          Shanachie
        - Yellowman - Nobody move nobody get hurt, 1984; SR-29426; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # GREL 71; A-side Matrix # GREL-71 A
        - Yellowman - Mi hot, 1991; SR-29427; Yellowman; Scorpio, Jack (Box 80)
          Catalog # DSR-11870; A-side Matrix # DSR-11870-A SIDE-MI HOT-GEOVANNI
          Black Scorpio
        - Yellowman - Duppy or gunman, 1982; SR-29428; Yellowman; Osbourne, Johnny (Box 80)
          Catalog # VPRD 1009; A-side Matrix # VPRLP 1009-A-1
        - Yellowman - Two giants clash, 1984; SR-29429; Yellowman; Wales, Josey (Box 80)
          Catalog # GREL 63; A-side Matrix # GREL 63 A
        - Yellowman - Under me fat thing, 1985; SR-29430; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # ARLP 013; A-side Matrix # DSA 5477 A
          Arrival
        - Yellowman - Confessions, 1983; SR-29431; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # VSLP 4048; A-side Matrix # VS LP 4048 A1
          Vista Sounds
          Middlesex, England
        - Yellowman - Yellow like cheese, 1987; SR-29432; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # RAS 3019; A-side Matrix # RAS-3019-A HUB
          Real Authentic Sound
          Washington, D.C.
        - Yellowman - Them a mad over me, 1982; SR-29433; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # LPJJ-060; A-side Matrix # JJ060 A
          J&L Records
        - Yellowman - Hotter reggae, 1982; SR-29434; Yellowman (Box 80)
          Catalog # JR-535; A-side Matrix # JR-516-A
          Jam Rock
        - Yellowman - King Yellowman meets the Mighty Josey Wales, 1983; SR-29435; Yellowman; Wales, Josey (Box 80)
          Catalog # ALP 009; A-side Matrix # D.S.R.-1556-B-YELLOW MAN MEET JOSE WHALES-THE GENTLE GENIUS
        - Yellowman - Rambo, 1986; SR-29436; Yellowman; Dunbar, Sly; Shakespeare, Robbie; Sly & Robbie (Box 80)
          Catalog # MT 003; A-side Matrix # MT-003-A
          Moving Target
        - Yellowman - Strong me strong; Disco reggae, 1984; SR-29437; Yellowman; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 80)
          Catalog # 44-04964; A-side Matrix # XSS-171595-1A
        - Yellowman - Strong me strong; Disco reggae, 1984; SR-29438; Yellowman; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 80)
        - Yellowman & Fathead - Show-down Vol. 5, 1984; SR-29439; Yellowman & Fathead; Yellowman (Box 81)
          Catalog # JJ-150; A-side Matrix # JJ150 A
          Empire Records
        - Yellowman & Fathead - The Yello, the Purple, the Nancy, 1982; SR-29440; Yellowman & Fathead; Yellowman; Purpleman; Sister Nancy (Box 81)
          Catalog # GREL 49; A-side Matrix # GREL 49 A
        - Yellowman & Fathead - For your eyes only, 1985; SR-29441; Yellowman & Fathead; Yellowman (Box 81)
          Catalog # ALP 004; A-side Matrix # D.S.R.6705-A-SPIDERMAN SURREY RECORDS
        - Yellowman & Fathead - Super mix, 1982; SR-29442; Yellowman & Fathead; Yellowman (Box 81)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # DSR-5364-A-DT-SONIC SOUNDS YELLOWMAN & FATHEAD LD
          Volcano
        - Yellow Magic Orchestra - After service (disc one), 1984; SR-29443; Yellow Magic Orchestra (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29444. Double album.
          Catalog # YLR-40001; A-side Matrix # YLP-40001A
          Tokyo, Japan
        - Yellow Magic Orchestra - After service (disc two), 1984; SR-29444; Yellow Magic Orchestra (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29443. Double album.
          Catalog # YLR-40002; A-side Matrix # YLP-40002A
        - Yellow Magic Orchestra - Service, 1983; SR-29445; Yellow Magic Orchestra (Box 81)
          Catalog # YLR-28013; A-side Matrix # YLR-28013A
        - Yellow Magic Orchestra - Cue; 1000 knives, 1981; SR-29446; Yellow Magic Orchestra (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29447. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-12039; A-side Matrix # AM-SP 012039-A S1
        - Yellow Magic Orchestra - Cue; 1000 knives, 1981; SR-29447; Yellow Magic Orchestra (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29446. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-12039; A-side Matrix # AM-SP 012039-A-P1
        - Yojo Working - Hold on (R&B selection), 1996; SR-29448; Yojo Working (Box 81)
          Catalog # SOMRB18; A-side Matrix # SOMRB 18 A-1
          Sound of Ministry
        - You Can Dance - You Can Dance, 1995; SR-29449; You Can Dance (Box 81)
          Catalog # 237-093; A-side Matrix # 273093 AI 1-479067 XSB-4264 17995
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Young & Company - Is it good to you?, 1981; SR-29450; Young & Company (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29451. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 783; A-side Matrix # 783-A
          Eastern Records
        - Young & Company - Is it good to you?, 1981; SR-29451; Young & Company (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29450. 2 copies.
        - Young Black Teenagers - Nobody knows Kelli; Proud to be Black, 1990; SR-29452; Young Black Teenagers (Box 81)
          Catalog # MCA-24073; A-side Matrix # MCA-10220-MD1
          Sound of Urban Listeners
        - Young Black Teenagers - Young Black Teenagers, 1991; SR-29453; Young Black Teenagers (Box 81)
          Catalog # MCA-10031; A-side Matrix # MCA-10568-MD1
        - Young, John Paul - Love is in the air, 1978; SR-29454; Young, John Paul (Box 81)
          Catalog # DSKO 126; A-side Matrix # ST-DSKO-35486-1
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - Young, Karen - Hot shot, 1978; SR-29455; Young, Karen (Box 81)
          Catalog # WE 105; A-side Matrix # WE-105-A
          West End Records
        - Michael Zager Band - Life's a party, 1978; SR-29456; Michael Zager Band (Box 81)
          Catalog # JC 35771; A-side Matrix # PAL-35771-2C
        - Michael Zager Band - Let's all chant, 1978; SR-29457; Michael Zager Band (Box 81)
          Catalog # PS 7013; A-side Matrix # PS-7013-A
          Private Stock
        - Zalmac - Whatcha gonna do, 1982; SR-29458; Zalmac (Box 81)
          Catalog # TS-5004; A-side Matrix # TS-5004-A
          The Sound of Brooklyn (TSOB)
        - Zapp - The new Zapp IV u, 1985; SR-29459; Zapp (Box 81)
          Catalog # 1-25327; A-side Matrix # 1-25327-A-SRI
        - Zapp - Zapp, 1980; SR-29460; Zapp (Box 81)
          Catalog # BSK 3463; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3463
        - Zapp - Zapp Vibe, 1989; SR-29461; Zapp (Box 81)
          Catalog # 1-25807; A-side Matrix # 1-25807-A-SRI
          Reprise Records
        - Zest - Hot tasty love, 1983; SR-29462; Zest (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29463. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JC 1001; A-side Matrix # 1001-A
          Jungle City Records
        - Zest - Hot tasty love, 1983; SR-29463; Zest (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29462. 2 copies.
        - Zeus & Osiris - Drop that, 1999; SR-29464; Zeus & Osiris (Box 81)
          Catalog # PBR 001; A-side Matrix # PBR-001-A
          Party Breaks Records
        - Z'looke - Take U back to my place, 1988; SR-29465; Z'looke (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29466. 2 copies.
          Catalog # D1-75600; A-side Matrix # DL-1-75600-21-DMM 1-2 B-33493-21-DMM
          Orpheus Records
        - Z'looke - Take U back to my place, 1988; SR-29466; Z'looke (Box 81)
          In same jacket as # SR-29465. 2 copies.
          Catalog # D1-75600; A-side Matrix # D1-1-75600-21-DMM 1-3
        - Zoo Nation - I'm in love, 1997; SR-29467; Zoo Nation; Johnson, D.M. (Box 81)
          Catalog # MTR 2045; A-side Matrix # MTR-2045-A LOGO
          Mantra Vibes
        - Zoom - Saturday, Saturday night, 1981; SR-29468; Zoom (Box 81)
          Catalog # PD-1-6343; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6343-AS-PW
        - Zouk All Stars - Zouk All Stars, 1987; SR-29469; Zouk All Stars (Box 81)
          Catalog # MGP 4029; A-side Matrix # MORA-4029 A
          Moradisc
        - Zouk Machine - Maldòn, 1989; SR-29470; Zouk Machine (Box 81)
          Catalog # 210 244; A-side Matrix # DM210244 A 1/9-89 II
          Ariola
        - Zouk Machine - Zouk Machine, 1986; SR-29471; Zouk Machine; Expérience 7 (Box 81)
          Catalog # HDD 2431; A-side Matrix # MPO 1 HDD 2431 A
          Debs
          Paris, France
        - Zouk Time - Zouk Time, 1988; SR-29472; Zouk Time (Box 81)
          Catalog # LM 6057; A-side Matrix # LM 6057 A
          Liso Musique Production
        - Zouk Time - Guetho à Liso, 1987; SR-29473; Zouk Time (Box 81)
          Catalog # LM 6048; A-side Matrix # LM 6048 A
        - Zulema - Z-licious, 1978; SR-29474; Zulema (Box 81)
          Catalog # LEJ-17000; A-side Matrix # SAHS 1734
          Lejoint
        - Zulu, Philemon - How long - Zulu jive, 1987; SR-29475; Zulu, Philemon (Box 81)
          Catalog # Shanachie-43048; A-side Matrix # SH-43048-A
          Newton, New Jersey
        - Zwei Komponenten - Wahrheit part 1, 2000; SR-29479; Zwei Komponenten; Da Poise (Box 81)
          Catalog # MVR 2000/001; A-side Matrix # MVR 2000/001 A1
          Mellowvibes Records
          Waltrop, Germany